

Date of birth: 10/06/1996 Address: Istanbul

Email: ahmetyldd@gmail.com

SUMMARY

Hello! Im Ahmet and Im living in Turkey. Let me briefly talk about myself, I love learning new technologies, languages and frameworks. I love programming from my childhood. I speak English very well like reading developer companies or open-source communities (Apache,Oracle etc.) features, new releases, version updates in short, their documentations. My Applications developed through Linux, therefore i have essential experience with Linux (Unix,bash commands) Most of my positions utilized agile-like development processes using JIRA.

WORK EXPERIENCE

2019 – present

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

(8 months)

Etiya Software

Designed and developed efficient and maintainable Software according to the business objectives and needs of the company's various clients. Creating core of product. To be more specific, Im currently working on project for Canada company and In this project, we use Spring Boot for api, Angular8 for frontend and PostgreSQL for database. This project is Turkey's largest software deal ever, and company is one of the top 5 telecommunications companies in Canada. There is five team in this project, and i am member of a team of 6.

2016 - 2017

INTERNSHIP

(Summer)

TRT

In this company I learned basics of Spring Core, Hibernate and Spring Data JPA

2015 - 2016

INTERNSHIP

(Summer)

BSD Software

I supported developers to for researchs like which tool we have to use or which framework. Creating entites, tables, relationships and some basic stuffs

EDUCATION

2002 - 2008

Computer Science - Bachelor's Degree

Selcuk University

SKILLS

Java 8

Spring Boot, MVC, Data JPA

Hibernate

Angular8 (Ngxs,Rxjs)

React (Redux)

Html, Css, Javascript

Oracle, PostgreSQL

Maven

Tomcat

Gitlab, Bitbucket

Agile

Jira, Confluence

PERSONAL

Proactive
Team-oriented
Hardworking
Friendly
Analytical